[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What funds were used in the founding of the British Museum?", "correct_answer": "National Lottery", "incorrect_answers": ["A single bequest of Lord Henry Dinsdale", "Fund raising among the nobility of Europe", "Multiple Royal bequests"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Pink is a song by Guns N Roses.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Una people are the last ones of the lost tribes remaining hidden away in the forest of New Guinea.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress played the role of a transgender man in the movie Boys Dont Cry?", "correct_answer": "Hilary Swank", "incorrect_answers": ["Helen Hunt", "Hally Berry", "Heather Graham"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This microscope part supports the glass slide and the specimen.", "correct_answer": "Stage clip", "incorrect_answers": ["Revolving nose piece", "Draw tube", "Arm"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the name of the computer program developed by the Hollywood division of the Los Angeles Police Department to create a  database of crimes, criminals, and all related information.", "correct_answer": "HITMAN", "incorrect_answers": ["ROBBER-E", "BEAT/COP", "BOOK-EM"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where does Martys older brother work in 1985 in the movie Back to the Future?", "correct_answer": "Burger King", "incorrect_answers": ["McDonalds", "Taco Bell", "Wendys"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the comedy classic Napoleon Dynamite, what was the name of Napoleons high school?", "correct_answer": "Preston High", "incorrect_answers": ["Shermer High", "Our Lady of Mercy", "P.S. 52"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film The Goonies, what is the name of Mrs. Walshs Hispanic maid who doesnt speak a word of English?", "correct_answer": "Rosalita", "incorrect_answers": ["Selena", "Maria", "Rosanna"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what 2 states was the 2007 movie Grindhouse was filmed?", "correct_answer": "Texas and California", "incorrect_answers": ["Texas and New York", "North Carolina and New York", "Georgia and Vermont"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Native American beliefs, humans could be transformed into a dangerous cannibalistic spirits if they ate human flesh. What is the name given to these creatures?", "correct_answer": "Wendigo", "incorrect_answers": ["Banshee", "Shaman", "Boggart"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these fictional dog characters was included in the American Film Institutess list of the greatest movie heroes of all time?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Lassie", "Strongheart", "Rin Tin Tin"]}]